{
	"title":"Traffic Safety",
	"index": "2",
	"category":"children",
	"questions":[
		{
			"question":"When riding in a car, I should always wear my seatbelt, booster seat, or car seat..",
			"correct":"YES",
			"incorrect":"NO",
			"result":"YES"
		},
		{
			"question":"It's okay to ride in the open bed of a pick-up truck.",
			"correct":"NO",
			"incorrect":"YES",
			"result":"NO - It's against the law.  See vehicle codes 21712 (a) driver and 21712 (b) passenger."
		},
		{
			"question":"You should look both ways before crossing the street.",
			"correct":"YES",
			"incorrect":"NO",
			"result":"YES"
		},
		{
			"question":"NEVER walk behind a school bus.",
			"correct":"YES",
			"incorrect":"NO",
			"result":"YES - The driver may not be able to see you."
		},
		{
			"question":"Does wearing seatbelts save lives.",
			"correct":"YES",
			"incorrect":"NO",
			"result":"YES"
		},
		{
			"question":"The safest place to cross a street is in the middle.",
			"correct":"NO",
			"incorrect":"YES",
			"result":"NO - The corner's where you cross the street.  If present, use the crosswalk."
		},
		{
			"question":"Young children should hold an adult's hand when crossing the (__________).",
			"correct":"BOTH PARKING LOT & STREET",
			"incorrect":"PARKING LOT",
			"incorrect":"LIVING ROOM",
			"incorrect":"STREET",
			"result":"BOTH PARKING LOT & STREET"
		},
		{
			"question":"The red light on a traffic signal means (__________).",
			"correct":"STOP",
			"incorrect":"GO",
			"incorrect":"SLOW",
			"incorrect":"CAUTION",
			"result":"STOP"
		},
		{
			"question":"It's okay to play on the railroad tracks.",
			"correct":"NO",
			"incorrect":"YES",
			"result":"NO - It can be dangerous and being on railroad property without permission is trespassing."
		},
		{
			"question":"The biggest factor in vehicle-train collisions is train speed.",
			"correct":"NO",
			"incorrect":"YES",
			"result":"NO - The biggest factor in collisions with thrains is driver error.  At a highway-rail intersection, roadway wehicles mucst always yield to trains."
		}
	]
}